Guide to the Murrysville Garden Club Records, 1952-2016 AIS.2016.05
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Scrapbooks, 1957-1963; XIII.
  - Scrapbook 2, 1966-1969 (Box 11, Volume 2)
  - Scrapbook 3, 1970-1972 (Box 11, Volume 3)
  - Scrapbook 4, 1995-1997 (Box 11, Volume 4)
- Garden Club Federation of Pennsylvania, 1979-2007; XIV.
  This series is composed of materials relating to the Garden Club Federation of Pennsylvania. The series includes a folder of plans and correspondence concerning the Governor's Residence Preservation Project in 2001 as well as two news booklets. One of these news booklets is a special edition for the 50th anniversary of the Garden Club Federation of Pennsylvania.
  - 50th Anniversary Booklet, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Governor's Residence Preservation, 1997-2001 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - News Booklet, Volume 38, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 20)